

# CONTACT

- 665810442
- ✓ maciekkusiak27@gmail.com
- Myślenice
- maciej-kusiak-21199b208/
- maciekkusiak27
- https://maciekkusiak27.github.io/ maciej-kusiak-cv/

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2019-2024

# CRACOW UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

- Bachelor of applied computer science
- Master of applied computer science

### 2015-2019

UPPER SECONDARY SCHOOL OF COMMUNICATIONS

• IT TECHNICIAN E12, E13, E14 EXAMS

## COURSES

- Angular The Complete Guide (2024 Edition) - Maximilian Schwarzmüller
- Programming samurai frontend courses - JS, HTML, CSS, React

# LANGUAGES

- Polish (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- German (Basics)

# **MACIEJ KUSIAK**

# JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

### **PROFILE**

I am a graduate of master's and bachelor's studies in engineering, specializing in applied computer science at the Krakow University of Technology. I have almost two years of experience working part-time as a front-end developer. I am looking for my first full-time job in an environment that will allow me to develop my skills and learn new technologies and solutions.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Futurum Technology Ltd Spk

November 2023 - August 2024

Junior Frontend Developer

- Development of healthcare app for radiologists
- Working in an international team of programmers
- Implementing new components, correcting errors
- Working with the client
- Website refactoring and rwd repair
- Angular, TypeScript, RxJs, SCSS, HTML, CSS, JS, Material Design, GitHub etc

### Comarch S.A.

July 2022- July 2023

Junior & Intern Frontend Developer

- Development of ERP management system
- Working in a scrum team
- Angular, TypeScript, RxJs, SCSS, HTML, CSS, JS, GitLab, Jira, internal design systems etc
- Own projects
  - Law Firm website available on the Internet. (JS, HTML, CSS)
  - Music band website ready to upload. (JS, HTML, CSS)
  - CV page, grouping all information about me on GH Pages. (Angular, SCSS, TS)
  - CV generator allowing you to download pdf files (in progress) (Angular, Tailwind CSS, TS)
  - An application that checks the departures of subsequent buses (Angular, TS, SCSS - in future also Ionic)
  - Application for managing reservations in a music studio (Angular, NestJs, TS, SCSS, Rest API)
  - An application verifying software license applications for the Krakow University of Technology (Angular, NestJs, TS, SCSS, Rest API)
  - Electron application that groups pages with job offers in a desktop application (ElectronJs)

In my own projects, I focus on learning new technologies and developing those I know. Some of the above are student projects, some are my own ideas. The technologies I use in my own projects are Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, RxJs, HTML, CSS, SCSS, but to a lesser extent I also try to use React, React Native or NativeScript, Ionic, Electron, NodeJs, NestJs and many others.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).